artspace.com 2015-06-29

# Artspace - Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

### INTRODUCTION

Welcome to Artspace and thank you for visiting. Artspace.com Markets, Inc., the owner of Artspace.com ("Artspace") is committed to providing you an enjoyable experience while maintaining your privacy. The information that we collect and store, helps us to enhance your shopping and browsing experience and provide you with information that is specific to your needs and preferences. Please read this entire Privacy Policy which will inform you about the types of information we collect, as well as how we will store, use and protect such information. By visiting the Site, you are agreeing the terms of our Privacy Policy. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") covers the Artspace website (the "Site") located at www.artspace.com and is part of our Terms of Use Agreement. Please click here to see that Agreement.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

### Information You Explicitly Provide to Us

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" is any information that identifies you personally would enable someone to contact you directly or describes your relationship with Artspace. We collect and store Personal Information when you register to use our Site, ask a questions, complete a form, tell us your preferences, conduct a transaction or send us an email. Such Personal Information may include your name, address, email address, date of birth, credit card information and other preferences you choose to provide us. When you register, you will also consent to receive email correspondence from us. We will use your Personal Information to complete transactions, respond to your requests, deliver the products and services you request, personalize the Site, allow you to view your past purchases and collections and to notify you of promotions, updates, news or special offers (which may be offered by Artspace or one of our partners) that we think may be of interest you. If you chose to invite a friend to join Artspace, you will need to provide us with his or her name and email address and you represent to us that you have their permission to do so. We will store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, tracking the success of our referral program and allowing you to track the success of your referral invitations. Your friend may contact us at unsubscribe@artspace.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

From time to time we may offer promotions, contests or sweepstakes on our site. If you choose to participate we may collect information including your name, address, age, telephone number, email address or other contact information. We would use this information to notify contest winners, award prizes, monitor site traffic, personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys) and to send participants an email newsletter. We may also request other information some of which may be optional. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company may not be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. Participation is subject to the Official Rules governing that promotion and we encourage you to read such Rules carefully.

During registration and participation in Site promotions, you are required to give truthful contact and demographic information in accordance with our Terms of Use.

By providing your Personal Information to us during your registration and thereafter during use of the Site, you expressly consent to Artspace's collection, use and storage of such information as stated in this Privacy Policy. If you wish to discontinue non-transactional email correspondence with us at any time, simply follow the instructions to "Unsubscribe" which appear in every email we send, or contact us through the Contact Us page or the email address indicated at the end of this policy.

Information Collected Automatically

### (i) Server Statistics.

Like many Web sites, we automatically collect general statistics about our Website traffic and store it in log files in order to track usage and user trends on our site. This information includes hits to our server, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), page views, navigational patterns, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data and the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to track users' movements around the Website so that we can communicate with our users in the most effective manner and provide them the most useful and desired features, functionality, products and services. In connection with this analysis, Artspace also uses devices called "web beacons" to help us identify when emails sent to you from us have been received and read. We may also collect IP addresses and other information in order to prevent the introduction of viruses and hackers into the Site.

When we collect this usage data, we typically only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. When IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information it is to offer customers the best user experience possible. We may also provide this data in aggregate form to partners, Artists and Institutions so that they can understand how often users are seeing their pages and buying their products on our Site.

### (ii) Cookies.

A cookie is a text file that is assigned by a web server and stored on a user's computer to uniquely identify the browser on a particular computer for record-keeping purposes. Artspace uses cookies to collect aggregate information about site usage, help identify users when they return to our site, track navigational patterns of usage and access user preferences. We do so to enhance the quality of your visit to our Site, access your preferences and personalize the Site for you.  
Artspace uses "session" or temporary cookies to ensure that you are recognized when you move from page to page on the site and that any information you enter on the Site (for example, items in your shopping cart) are not lost as you navigate the site. We also use persistent cookies so we can remember you on subsequent visits to our Site, which enables us to provide a more enhanced, efficient and personal experience when you return to our Site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our Site.

If you do not want to have cookies placed on your computer, you can set your browser to refuse or remove cookies by following the instructions in your browser's "help" file. However, doing so will limit system performance, may not allow you to take advantage of certain features on our Site and even cause certain features of the Site to malfunction.

We may permit limited third parties to place cookies through the Site to provide us with better insights into the use of the Site, user demographics, or to provide relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information about a consumer's online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our Site.

We do not use technology that recognizes do-not-track signals from your web browser.

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

As noted above, we use the data we collect in order to provide you with the best web experience possible. We only use the information we collect in the manner described above this Privacy Policy and as follows.

i) We may share your information with selected vendors and business partners with whom we work ("Service Providers"). These Service Providers provide functions on our behalf such as fulfillment, shipping, credit card processing, data and tracking analysis, customer service, market services etc in order to complete the transactions and offer you the best service our Site.  
ii) We may use your personal and transactional information internally for our business purposes, including among other things, to offer our own, our affiliates' or third-party products and services that we think you may find of interest. We may use your email address to contact you to respond to your customer service inquiries. You can elect not to receive emails from by unsubscribing to our emails or by contacting us as indicated below.  
iii) As noted above, we may provide aggregate statistics, which do not include Personal Information, about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related Site information to reputable third party vendors. We sometimes use this aggregated data (such as what areas of our Site are visited most frequently, what services are most used, what products are most popular and how often our emails are opened etc.) for research and commercial purposes. This information helps us develop a better site that is more useful and accessible to you as well as offer better products and services to you but is never associated with any Personally identifiable information.  
iv) We only reveal Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties if: (1) you request or authorize it; (2) the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); or as stated in this privacy policy.

### USER GENERATED CONTENT

You may choose to participate in areas of our Site dedicated to user-generated content that we provide you to enjoy. By "User Content" we mean any content you post to the site, which may include reviews, comments, image uploading, captions, participating in forums, curating or creating art collections and other such features that allow you to add content to the site. Any User Content you voluntarily disclose for other users to view on the Site is not Personal Information. It becomes publicly available information and can be read, collected, redistributed or used by any person for any purpose. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable or other information you choose to submit as User Content and we reserve the right to remove any User Content generated by any user at our sole discretion.

### COLLECTING INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN

This Site is not designed nor intended to be attractive to use by children under the age of 18 ("Minors"). We do not knowingly collect information from Minors. If you are under the age of 18, you are not authorized to use this site so please do not submit any information to us.

### CONSENT TO PROCESSING

Your Personal Information may be processed by us in the country where it was collected as well as other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding data protection may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By using this site and by providing any Personal Information to the Site, all users, including without limitation users in Canada and the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States.

### ACCESS AND SECURITY

If you are a registered user of this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password. If you use this site, you are responsible for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security. We reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, or remove or edit content in our sole discretion.

We use reasonable physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to help us protect the security, integrity and confidentiality of data stored on our system. The Site encrypts your credit card number and other Personal Information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology to provide for the secure transmission of the information from your PC to our servers. SSL is an industry-standard protocol for encryption over the Internet. While no system is 100% secure, we believe that the measures we have implemented minimize the risk of security breach to an appropriate level given the types of information involved. Please note that any information you provide us by email is unencrypted.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA RIGHTS

As stated in this Privacy Policy, we may share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you tell us not to. To opt out of such sharing please contact us at the address below.

### EXTERNAL LINKS

We may offer links to the websites sites of other companies but we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites, nor are we responsible for how these other companies collect, use, disclose or secure the information you provide them. If you choose to access a third party website linked to or from our Site, you do so at your own risk. We do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or web sites.

### MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Artspace may amend or change this Privacy Policy from time to time at our sole discretion. We encourage you to check our Site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect and any changes that may have been made to them. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will post the revised Policy and the revised effective date here. Your continued use of the Site and provision of any Personal Information after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such Privacy Policy change.

### CONTACTING US

This site is owned and operated by Artspace.com Markets, Inc. If you have any questions or suggestions with respect to this policy, or if you wish to ask us to delete, correct, or show you your information as provided above, please email us at privacy@artandculture.com or write to us at our corporate address:

65 Bleecker Street, 8th Floor  
New York, NY 10012
